<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Welcome to The SyncE Projects on SyncE Projects</title><link>https://qqq.sync-e.nwtime.org/</link><description>Recent content in Welcome to The SyncE Projects on SyncE Projects</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://qqq.sync-e.nwtime.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>401 - Unauthorized Access</title><link>https://qqq.sync-e.nwtime.org/401/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://qqq.sync-e.nwtime.org/401/</guid><description>This page requires a login as an authorized user.</description></item><item><title>403 - Forbidden</title><link>https://qqq.sync-e.nwtime.org/403/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://qqq.sync-e.nwtime.org/403/</guid><description>You do not have permission to view this page.</description></item><item><title>404 - Page Not Found</title><link>https://qqq.sync-e.nwtime.org/404/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://qqq.sync-e.nwtime.org/404/</guid><description>Oops! We couldn&amp;rsquo;t find that page.
Please check the URL or try searching for related content using the search box at the top of this page.</description></item><item><title>500 - Internal Server Error</title><link>https://qqq.sync-e.nwtime.org/500/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://qqq.sync-e.nwtime.org/500/</guid><description>The web server encountered an error that prevented it from loading this page. Please try again later.
If the issue persists, you can report the error to webmaster.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://qqq.sync-e.nwtime.org/syncesmc/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://qqq.sync-e.nwtime.org/syncesmc/about/</guid><description>About About
Documentation</description></item><item><title>Documentation</title><link>https://qqq.sync-e.nwtime.org/synced/documentation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://qqq.sync-e.nwtime.org/synced/documentation/</guid><description>Table of Contents Hardware Software Configuration Management API Event Callback Functions Acronyms Hardware Figure 1. Hardware inter-connection between SyncE ports, external clocks, inputs, outputs, the DPLL device, and the CPU running synced application.
One or more external multiplexers can be used to connect multiple SyncE ports to a clock.
The multiplexers can be both single-output or dual-output:
Those ports connected to external multiplexers, which are not associated to a clock, are called SyncE monitoring ports.</description></item><item><title>Documentation</title><link>https://qqq.sync-e.nwtime.org/syncesmc/documentation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://qqq.sync-e.nwtime.org/syncesmc/documentation/</guid><description>Documentation Table of Contents Overview Synchronization Network Topology Why SyncESMC Architecture Design Goals Configuration Packet Engine ESMC State Machine External MUX for Input Signals Hardware Abstraction Layer External Interface Overview ESMC is a Logical Channel which transmits SSM information. The SSM information determines the Quality level of EEC. It is based on ITU-T G.8264 (03/2018) and ITU-T G.781 (04/2020) Ethernet SSM is ITU-T-defined Ethernet Slow Protocol.</description></item></channel></rss>